Neurodiversity describes the
idea that people experience
and interact with the world
around them in different ways.
There is no one right way of thinking,
learning, and behaving, and these
differences are not to be viewed as
deficits.
It's important for
all of us to foster an
environment that is
conducive to neurodiversity.
We need to recognize and emphasize each
and every person's individual strengths
and talents, and provide support for their
differences and requirements.
People with neurological
differences are not
broken or incomplete
versions of normal people.
We're all born different
and raised differently.
Hence, all of us are to
some extent differently abled.
Neurodiversity is a normal and natural
variation in the human genome.
The distinctiveness of
neurodiverse people isn't
something that necessarily
needs to be cured.
Neurodiverse employees merely
need some help and accommodation.
They may bring new
perspectives to an
organization's efforts to
create or recognize value.
In this course, you will
recognize the value that
neurodiverse employees
add to an organization.
You'll understand how to
educate your employees about
neurodiversity and create
an inclusive workplace.
You'll learn to examine
strategies for providing
equal access to
neurodiverse employees.